《铁血战士》
哨兵一号  收到
Picket One, copy.
是否发现人质
Do you got eyes on the hostages?
依然没有发现
Still negative.
赌20块他们不会露面
20 bucks says they don't show.
你们两个白痴真当要拿
You two morons really making bets
贩毒集团会不会处决人质来打赌吗
on whether a drug cartel has executed these hostages?
可不他妈是嘛
Abso-fucking-lutely.
你是在试探我们吧
I believe that was implied. Yeah.
就确认一下  我赌20块
Just checking. I'm in for 20.
发现两名人质
I got two hostages.
没有其他人
No crosswind.
我不等了  准备射击
I'm not waiting. 10-50, out.
蓝凫二号  你们在吗
Bluebill Two, are you out there?
完毕
Over.
该死的
Goddamn it!
杜普雷  天啊
Dupree, Jesus!
海恩斯呢
Where's Haines?
不知道  通讯断了
Don't know. Comm's not fucking working.
把包给我
Give me the pack.
这是证据
It's evidence.
没人会相信这个的
Ain't nobody gonna believe this one.
这他妈是什么  上尉
The fuck is that, Cap?
不是我们该知道的
It's above our pay grade.
海恩斯  过来  完毕
Haines! Come in. Over.
海恩斯  该死的快过来  完毕
Haines, goddamn it, come in. Over!
长官
Sir?
这他妈是什么  上尉
The fuck is that, Cap?
通讯他妈的断了
Comm's not fucking working.
海恩斯
Haines?
开火
Light it up!
各位  记住
Gentlemen, remember...
它们体型很大  移动很快
they're large, they're fast,
手段非常残忍
and fucking you up's their idea of tourism!
行动
Go!
都听好了
Eyes up! Come on!
乘客  飞行器  都要找到
I want the passenger. I want the pod.
要是它是天外来物
If it's not from here...
-你要带回去  -我要带回去
- You want it. - ...I want it.
我需要帮助
I need help.
我有钱
And I have money.
好吧
All right.
我要你帮我把这个寄出去
I need you to mail this for me.
寄到这个地址
You send it to this address.
把包里的东西寄走  不是背包
Mail what's in the pack, not the backpack.
快去吧
Ahora. Go!
退后
Back up!
太神奇了
It was so amazing!
是的
Yeah, it was.
(罗伦斯·A·戈登中学)
再见  妈妈
Bye, Mom!
-快点拉  -不要  你拉
- Do it, man. - No, you do it.
好吧
Okay.
快拉
Do it.
该死的
Oh, shit.
瞧啊  瞧啊
Looky, looky, loo.
EJ  你饿了吗
Hey, EJ, you hungry?
我饿得想揍屁股蛋儿了
I'm hungry for an ass-burger.
听起来挺不错的
Mmm. Sounds delicious.
又大又美味的屁股蛋儿
A nice, big, juicy ass-burger.
没错
Oh, yeah.
你在干什么
The hell are you doing?
-他没救了  -好吧
- He's a goner. - All right.
(刚花了1个半小时把家里打扫好  要是你弄乱了  我就宰了你 亲亲抱抱 妈妈)
你好啊
Hi, there.
奎因·麦肯纳住在这里吗
Does, uh, Quinn McKenna live here?
他的邮箱付费到期了
His post office box payments are past due.
国防部寄来的
Department of Defense.
他为政府工作  是吗
He works for the government, does he?
Mos-1-1-b-3-v-w-3
Mos-1-1-b-3-v-w-3.
军事指派
Military designation.
他杀人
He kills people...
好让你安心当邮递员
so you can be a mailman.
(马里兰州  约翰·霍普金斯大学)
布拉克特博士吗
Dr. Brackett?
我了解到你很喜欢占星学
I understand you enjoy stargazing?
我的人会照顾好你的狗
My men will take care of your dog.
请跟我走一趟
Will you come with me, please?
这是什么
What am I looking at?
就是你心里想的那个  没错
It's exactly what you think it is. Yeah.
它们以前就来过
They've been here before.
1987年  1997年
'87, '97.
最近它们造访的频率提高了
Lately, the visits are increasing in frequency.
罗利  我回来了  我给你买了东西
Rory, I'm home! Hey, I got you something.
你放学后做了一本吗
Did you do one of these after school?
全都做好了
I did all of them.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
我买了两个你来选
Well, I got you two options.
这里有
We have...
海盗面具  还有
pirate, or...
科学怪人面具
Frankenstein.
弗兰肯斯坦  你知道吧  绿色的皮肤
Frankenstein, you know, green skin?
他把一个女孩扔到水里想看她会不会浮起来
Threw a girl to see if she would float?
不知道  好吧
No. Okay.
那就选海盗面具吧  好吗
Well, let's go with pirate. Yeah?
太傻了
This is dumb.
他们会
The guys will...
他们还是看得到
They will still be able to see.
看得到什么
See what?
看得到是我
That it's me.
你曾经这么说过
You were once quoted as saying,
"我从母亲的子宫里掉了下来
"I dropped from my mother's womb...
我撞到了地板
I hit the floor...
我开始爬过敌人的领地
and I started crawling
走向我的坟墓"
through hostile territory toward my grave."
说得很好
About right, yeah.
-太牛了  -相当病态
- That's badass. - It's pretty morbid.
很黑暗
It's pretty dark.
测谎仪是拿来做什么的
What's with the polygraph?
我以为这是心理评估
I thought this was a psych eval.
我们必须知道你是否构成威胁
We need to know if you pose a threat.
我是狙击手
Oh, I'm a sniper.
我的目标可不就是制造威胁吗
Isn't posing a threat kind of the fucking point?
你大多数时间都在全国各地执行任务
You spend most of your time now in-country...
远离你的妻子和儿子吗
estranged from your wife and son?
听着  我明白
Look, I get it.
有东西掉到了墨西哥  不希望有任何目击者
Something went down in Mexico and nobody wants any witnesses.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你不是来检查我疯没疯的
You're not here to find out if I'm crazy.
你是想让我闭紧嘴巴
You wanna make sure the label sticks.
那么你是觉得你是被迫的吗
So, you feel you're being railroaded?
这也太明显了
I can see the tracks on the floor!
我声明我没疯  地上没铁轨
I don't see tracks on the floor, for the record.
你觉得你是自己星球上的
You feel like you're a stranger
一个陌生人  是吗  上尉
on your own planet, don't you, Captain?
你是说就像外星人吗
Like an alien, you mean?
你想要的不就是这个吗
That's what you wanted.
我能来块饼干吗
Do I get a cookie now?
他看到了
He saw something.
-没错  -嗯
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah.
你再推我一下  我就打断你的脖子
You shove me again, I'm gonna break your neck.
我不小心说出口了吗
Did I say that out loud?
麦肯纳
McKenna.
最后一个
Last one.
谢谢你的好意  谢谢
Thanks for your kindness. Thank you.
你没事吧
You all right over there?
没事  不用担心他  他得了秽语抽动症
No, don't worry about him. He's just got Tourettes.
-他控制不住  -操你妈  柯伊尔
- He can't control it. - Fuck you, Coyle.
你得习惯  兄弟
You get used to it, bro.
欢迎加入第二团
Welcome to Group Two.
这是什么意思
Oh, yeah? What's that?
像一个小队
Like a unit?
不是  团体  第二团
No, group. Group Two.
团体治疗  第二诊室
Group therapy, room two.
-麦肯纳  -内布拉斯加·威廉姆斯
- McKenna. - Nebraska Williams.
这是你的真名吗
That's your real name?
盖洛德
Gaylord.
-这名字不错  -我也觉得
- That's a good call, then. - Yeah, I thought so.
你在哪儿服役的
Where did you serve?
2003年  阿富汗"持久自由行动"
Operation Enduring Freedom, '03.
为塔利班而去  为鸦片留下了
Went for the Taliban, stayed for the opium.
那是柯伊尔  误伤友军
That's Coyle. Friendly fire incident.
一回头打中了自家军队的车
Got turned around, fired at one of his own vehicles.
他现在负责讲笑话
Now, he tells jokes.
他叫林奇
That's Lynch.
因在摩苏尔炸毁半座山被表彰
Got a medal for blowing up half a mountain in Mosul.
熵
Entropy.
那是我的拿手好戏
That's my game.
都快失败了
Things like to fall apart
而我  扭转了战局
and I... make it happen.
就像这样
Just... Just like that.
别
Don't.
别这样
他叫奈特尔斯
That's Nettles.
好吧  我叫奈特尔斯
Okay, I'm Nettles.
作为直升机飞行员出征三次
Did three tours flying Hueys.
他可热爱圣经了  对吧  奈迪
He loves his Bible. Hey, Netty?
到造物的终结时刻了吗
Is it end times yet?
你们就笑吧
Yeah, laugh all you want.
但造物主都看着你们呢
But when you're standing at attention before your Maker...
我造她之前也看着她呢
I always stand at attention before I make her.
上帝造烂人
God makes shitty people.
真的
Yeah.
不然人类为什么会制造战争
I mean, why do you think people make war?
为什么  巴克斯利  为什么我们要制造战争
Why, Baxley? Why do we make war?
-你说  巴克斯利  -因为操鸡鸡
- Come on, Baxley! - Because fuck-cock-cock!
-因为我们操鸡鸡  -对  我们操鸡鸡
- Because we fuck cock-cock? - Yes, we fuck cocks.
没错  因为我们操鸡鸡
That's it, because we fuck cocks,
就是因为这个  所以我们不开心了
that's why. We get upset.
你是怎么进来这个烂地方的
How'd you snag a ticket on this shitmobile?
给一个指挥官来了一枪
Put a bullet in a CO.
有特定的原因吗
Any particular reason?
他是个混蛋
He was an asshole.
(占星师计划)
头低下
Keep your head down.
戴上这个
Here, throw this on.
这是你的幻觉吗
Is it just your imagination?
还是这个鬼地方真的在移动
Or is this haunted room actually stretching?
每次都要他妈说一遍吗
Every fucking time?
请注意
Your attention, please.
GRC会议已移至第3区A室
The GRC meeting has been moved to section 3, room A.
你来了
Aha! There you are!
欢迎  我是肖恩·坎耶
Welcome. I'm Sean Keyes.
我听说你写了一本
Wow. I heard you basically wrote the book
进化生物学的书
on evolutionary biology.
抱歉  我能不能...
Um, I'm sorry, can I just...
那是...
Is that...
天哪
Oh, my God!
该死的
Holy shit.
这是外星科技
That's alien technology.
你带我来是想让我看这个
This is what you brought me here to see?
是的
Well, yeah.
我能  我能看看吗  能接触吗
Can I... Can I see this? Can I get into this?
博士
Doc.
走吧
Let's go.
-一切都好吧  -是的  长官
- Everything good? - Yes, sir.
怎么了
What is it?
布拉克特博士
Dr. Brackett.
想来见一见掠夺者吗
Would you like to meet a Predator?
来吧
Come on.
请执行
Please observe
净化操作
decontamination protocol.
他们是怎么说服你前来帮忙的
So, how'd they rope you into this?
我6岁时给总统写了一封信
I wrote a letter to the president when I was six.
告诉他我有多喜欢动物
Told him how much I loved animals,
要是航空航天局发现了外星动物
and that if NASA ever found a space animal,
希望他们能给我打电话
they should call me.
几年前我因为一篇杂交菌株的论文
Couple years ago, I was put on a short list
上了候选人名单
for a paper I wrote on hybrid strains.
电脑对照参照了那封信  我就来这儿了
Computer cross-referenced the letter, and... here I am.
布拉克特博士
Dr. Brackett.
多谢前来
Thanks for coming.
相信你心里一定充满了疑问
I'm sure you have questions.
-其实只有两个问题  -好吧
- Oh. Just two, actually. - Okay.
为什么你叫它"掠夺者"
Why do you call it "The Predator"?
是一个昵称
It's a nickname.
数据显示它会追捕猎物
You know, the data suggests that it tracks its prey.
利用猎物的弱点
Exploits weakness.
它看起来
Seems to...
乐在其中
well, enjoy it.
就像是在玩游戏
Like a game.
这不是掠夺者  而是娱乐猎人
That's not a predator, that's a sports hunter.
什么
Sorry?
掠夺者捕猎只是为了生存
A predator kills its prey to survive.
你形容的就像是捕鲈鱼的渔夫
I mean, what you're describing is more like a bass fisherman.
我们投票表决了  掠夺者听起来更酷  对吧
Well, we took a vote. Predator's cooler, right?
-对极了  -对极了
- Fuck yeah. - Fuck yeah.
在墨西哥发现了它的逃生舱
Found his escape pod in Mexico.
我们还在找它开来的飞船
Still looking for the ship he came in.
它已经深度麻醉了
He's heavily sedated.
你这个美丽的混蛋
You are one beautiful motherfucker.
我猜你的第二个问题是为什么找你
I'm gonna guess your second question is, why are you here?
我们的检测结果有一些...奇怪
Our test results yielded something a little... odd.
这是个玩笑吗
Is this a joke?
我们做了十次基因组序列
We ran the genome sequence ten times.
这个外星人有
This specimen has...
-人类的基因  -没错
- Human DNA? - Yeah.
是的
Yeah.
我们知道物种会自发形成
Look, we know about spontaneous speciation.
大多数植物和昆虫都是这样  但是...
Mostly plants and insects, but...
但是一些哺乳动物  绵羊  山羊
But some mammals, sheep, goats, uh...
对
Yeah.
红狼是众所周知的混血动物
The red wolf is known to be a hybrid
是由土狼和灰狼
between the coyote and the grey wolf...
或者可能是某种形式的重组技术
Or possibly some form of recombinant technology...
各位  各位  各位  我明白了
Guys, guys, guys. I get it, I get it.
你们想知道是不是有人操了外星人
You wanna know if someone fucked an alien?
对
Yeah.
它戴了大气面罩
Okay, it's got some kind of atmospheric mask,
生物气密罩  还有
biohelmet, and...
这些是什么  护腕吗
What are these? Like, some kind of wrist gauntlets?
是的
Exactly.
那头盔和还有一只护腕呢
So, where's the helmet and the other gauntlet?
相信我们  已经到处都找过了
We've looked, believe me.
这是谁
Who is this?
他是一个接触掠夺者的人
He made first contact with the Predator.
好  我要找他谈谈
Great. I'd like to talk to him.
他正在接受评估  所以...
Well, he's being evaluated, so...
好吧
Okay.
在你们给他做脑叶切断术之前
Well, before you lobotomize him,
我想问他几个问题
I'd like to ask him a few questions.
收到重新规划路线指令
We have a request to reroute.
收到  目的地是哪里
Read you five-by-five. Destination?
斯塔克韦瑟大坝  立即前往
Starkweather Dam. Proceed at once.
到时会有军队人员接应  完毕
You'll be met by military personnel. Over.
巴克斯利
Hey, Baxley!
有个问题问你
Question for ya.
又来了
All right, here we go.
你要怎么样才能给一个流浪汉割包皮
How do you circumcise a homeless man?
又来了
Here it comes.
踢你妈的下巴
Kick your mom in the chin.
操你妈  操你妈
Fuck your mother... Fuck your mother...
-都他妈给我闭嘴  -好吧
- Shut the fuck up! - All right.
你他妈给我闭嘴
You shut the fuck up.
好了  好了  玩笑开过头了
Hold on, hold on, hold on. Y'all going too fucking much.
我只想知道这个混蛋是谁
I just wanna know who this motherfucker is.
你是为什么进来的
Why are you here?
别这样  这里一车都是疯子
Come on, man, this is the loony bus.
-瞧瞧这个混蛋  -都是疯子
- Look at this motherfucker. - Loonies!
都是疯子
Loonies, yeah.
我跟外星人打了一架
I had a run-in with a space alien.
见鬼了
Oh, shit!
-不  让他  -他赢了
- No, let him... - Okay, that guy wins.
我听到过的最棒的故事
That's the best story I've ever heard.
太经典了
Classic story...
赢家已经诞生
That's the winner right there. Fuckin' hell.
你们能不能他妈的闭嘴
Would you shut the fuck up?
他们想要掩盖这件事
They want to put a lid on it,
所以我到了这儿
so here I am.
困在第二团里
Stuck in Group Two.
第二团的后来人  更蠢
The sequel to Group One, only stupider.
给他递根雪茄吧
Give this man a fuckin' cigar.
他妈的闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
"你们能不能他妈的闭嘴"
"Would you shut the fuck up?"
阴谋论
It's a conspiracy.
有外星人对吧
The goddamn space aliens, huh?
你在下面干什么  罗利
What are you doing down there, Rory?
玩...玩游戏
Uh, just... just playing games.
晚饭要凉了
Well, dinner's getting cold.
少校
Major?
有奇怪的不明飞行物  长官
Weird-ass bogey, sir.
上一秒还在雷达上  下一秒就不见了
One second it's on the grid, the next it's ghosting.
该死的
Damn it.
需要空中支援
We need something in the air.
给我连北美太空防御司令部
Get me NORAD.
我感觉研究里漏掉了什么东西
I feel like I'm missing something in the research.
我有什么没看到的
There's something I'm just not seeing.
听着  要是这个是血  我认为...
Look, if this is the blood, okay, I think--
你能告诉我那是什么吗
can you just tell me what that is?
因为之前
Because I was trying
我想接触一下  可有人不让我碰
to get into this earlier, but somebody stopped me.
他对我翻了个白眼
He gave me the hairy eyeball.
-就是那个人  -先等一下
- That guy actually. - Hold that thought.
长官  北美太空防御司令部报告异常不明飞行物
Sir, NORAD's reporting a 202 anomaly
可能正朝我们飞来
possibly heading our direction.
冲这里来的吗
Is it coming here?
老天  希望不是这样
God, I hope not.
该死的
Holy shit!
现在距离多远
How far away are we talking about?
未知  但是肯定是朝你们去了
Unknown. But it's definitely heading your way.
二级警报
Level two alert.
-二级警报  -该死的
- Level two alert. - Shit!
出什么事了
Hey, what's happening?
接近警报  不明飞行物入境  距离200英里
Proximity alert. Bogey's inbound. Range 200 miles.
锁定位置
Lock it down.
它醒了  它醒了  它醒了
He's awake! He's awake! He's awake!
按住它  按住它
Hey, hold him down! Keep him down!
按住它
Hold him down!
该死的
Oh, shit!
博士  快跟我走
Doc, on me, now!
快  快走
Move! Move!
CTJ
Church, Thomas, J.
快跑
Move!
请执行
Please observe
净化操作
decontamination protocol.
门已关闭  请脱掉外衣
Chamber secure. Remove outer garments.
CTJ
Church, Thomas, J.
请执行净化操作
Please observe decontamination protocol.
所有人员注意  橙色警报
All personnel, Code Orange.
橙色警报
Code Orange.
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
先停一下  里面发生了事故
Sit tight. There's been a breach.
知道要多久吗
Do you have an estimate?
现在还不行
Not right now.
我来火力掩护
I'll give you cover fire.
干倒它
Get him out!
来了  正前方
Movement, twelve o'clock!
别让它跑了
Don't let him get away.
我的外星动物别想跑
Not my space animal.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
外星人
Alien.
你说的外星人
Your green boy?
没错
Yep.
该死的外星人
Goddamn space aliens.
什么  什么
What? What?
你他妈没看到吗
Did you not just fucking see that, man?
我疯了吗
Am I going fucking mad?
闭嘴
Shut up.
-冷静  -我没看到
- Take it easy, man. - I didn't fucking see it.
奈特尔斯  安静
Nettles, be quiet.
它在哪里  我想看
Where the fuck is it? I wanna see it.
就是那东西杀了我的人
That's the thing that killed my men.
它们天性如此
Yeah, they'll do that.
我们得下车  我们得跑
We gotta get off this thing. We gotta move.
兄弟  这是辆车
Brother, it's a bus.
车能跑
It moves.
巴克斯利
Hey, Baxley!
要是你妈的阴道是个电子游戏
If your mom's vagina were a video game,
那分级肯定是人人能玩
it'd be rated "E" for "Everyone."
别吵了
Knock it off.
五个黑人大汉
What's the difference between
和笑话的区别是什么
five big black guys and a joke?
巴克斯利的妈妈开不起玩笑
Baxley's mom can't take a joke.
你说什么  混蛋
What, motherfucker!
来啊  贱人
Come on, bitch!
所有人  趴在地上
Everyone, on the floor, face down!
趴在地上  快
Face down! Now! Come on!
钥匙
Keys!
枪
Gun!
奈特尔斯  奈特尔斯  停下
Hey! Nettles! Nettles! Wait, hey! Hey!
你已经打倒他了  已经打倒他了  兄弟
You got him, all right? You got him, brother.
内布拉斯加  介意绕个道吗
Hey, Nebraska, you mind, uh, making a detour?
怎么  要去找你的外星人
What, for your green boy?
我是个狙击手  只要靠近点就行
I'm a sniper, just get me close, baby.
-你想杀了它  -那是当然
- You wanna kill him? - Oh, yeah!
你怎么不早说
Why didn't you just say so, man?
你要杀外星人
You're gonna kill a fucking alien?
坐稳了
Hey. Hold on.
操
Fuck!
这他妈是什么
Yo, what the fuck is that?
慢点  慢点
Easy, easy. Hey! Hey!
找掩护
Take cover!
躲到车后面
Behind the fucking bus!
你在上面干什么  跳下来  我接着你
What are you doing up there? Come on. Come on, I got you.
-我接着你  女士  -好
- Yep. I got you, lady. - Okay.
走吧  快  快点
Let's go! Hey. Come on, come on.
该死的
Goddamn it.
-抱歉  -快走
- Sorry. - Move!
该死的
Damn.
去直升机那里
Get to the choppers!
占星师  发现目标女性
Stargazer, I got eyes on the woman.
请求指令
Instructions?
消灭目标
Eliminate her.
寻回所有违禁品
Retrieve any contraband.
收到  占星师
Roger that, Stargazer.
对  好了  妹子
That's it, that's it, girl.
内布拉斯加
Hey, Nebraska!
给我吧
Got it.
你们后面没事吧
Everything okay back there?
你们这些混蛋
You fucking guys.
我们藏在这里
We found the one place to hide out
不会被人当做疯子
where we don't look crazy.
我已经很久没握过枪了
It's been a long time since I had a gun in my hand.
什么感觉
What's it feel like?
枪的感觉
Like a gun.
你觉得她跟他们在一起安全吗
Hey, you think she's safe in there with them?
那妹子吗
The girl?
他们是士兵
They're soldiers, man.
睡女人吗  不会的  兄弟
Sleeping ladies? Nah, bro.
坐吧
Sit down.
给
Here.
这是终结时刻了吧
It's the end of times, huh?
终结时刻最糟糕的一点是
Worst thing about the end times...
永远没有终结
they never fucking are.
那
So, um...
他活下来了吗
did he live?
你说什么
Say again?
那个指挥官  你射的那个混蛋活下来了吗
The CO? The asshole you shot, did he live?
是的  他活下来了
Yeah. He did.
那他现在在哪里
Yeah, and where is he at now?
你在骗我
You're shitting me.
我没打中他
I missed.
你为什么要这么做
Why did you do that?
-没打中吗  -不  对自己开枪
- Miss? - No, shoot yourself.
医生问了我同样的问题
Doctors asked me the same thing.
我带着头上的子弹自己走到了医院
Walked to the hospital with a bullet in my skull.
真是好时光
Good times.
我该担心吗
Should I be worried?
也许吧
Probably.
-来了  -你明白吗
- There we go. - Did you get that?
-放得离她手太近了  -对对对
- That's too close to her hand. - Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
她会撒到床上的
But then she's gonna drop that there.
各位
Guys!
你们在干什么  什么鬼
What the hell are you doing? What is all that shit?
我们想让她感觉自在点
We're trying to make her feel comfortable.
快走开
Come on.
她快醒了  醒来会看到
She's gonna wake up and see
一群混蛋围在身边  快走
a bunch of motherfuckers. Come on.
你在干什么
What are you doin'?
奈特尔斯  奈特尔斯
Nettles! Nettles!
快走
Move!
快点
快走开
Get out of there!
早上好  阳光宝贝
Morning, sunshine.
我真的希望不要有人再这么叫我了
I really wish people would stop calling me that.
冷静
Chill, hey!
我就说她会拿枪  10块钱
I told you she'd grab it. Ten bucks!
都交出来
Pay up! Whoo!
见鬼了
Fuck it, fuck it.
-我的手机呢  -你用不上的
- Where's my phone? - You're not gonna need that.
这可不好
Oh, that's not cool.
没事的
It's okay.
我说了没事的
I said it's okay.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
-把枪给我  -不  不要
- Give me the gun. - No. No.
她扣动了...
Oh, she pulled...
该死的  我就说她会扣动扳机
Oh! Shit, I told you she'd pull the trigger!
我该跟你们打赌的
I should have bet you that time!
我喜欢她  我喜欢她
I like her. I like her.
我该跟你们打赌的
I should have bet you that time!
-我喜欢她  -我喜欢她
- I like her. - I like her.
我喜欢她  我很喜欢她
I like her. I like her a lot.
给我  笨蛋
Give me that, ding-dong.
干得漂亮  妹子
Oh, shit! Attagirl.
什么  你是科学家  他们让你研究什么
What? You're a scientist, huh? What they got you working on?
你在外面活不过一天
You're not gonna last a day out there!
怎么  你觉得自己很特别
What, you think you're special?
刚才在大坝里  他们差点就把你打得脑袋开花
Back at the dam, they were gonna put a bullet in your head.
他们那时要射杀她
They were gonna shoot her?
对
Yes.
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
让开  回见
Get out of the way. See you around.
吃你个逼
Eat your pussy.
慢着  什么
Wait, what?
你好吗
How you doing?
不  你刚刚说"吃你个逼"
No, you just said, "Eat your pussy."
-你好吗  -不  你叫我吃你个逼
- How you doing? - No, you said, "Eat my pussy."
这人什么毛病
What the fuck is wrong with him?
-我是说你很固执  -他说你很固执
- I said you're pushy. - He said you're pushy.
不  你说吃你个逼
No, you said, "Eat your pussy."
不  我说的是"嘘  你很固执"
No. I said, "Sheesh! You're pushy!"
不  你说吃你个逼
No, you said, "Eat my pussy."
不  他说的就是那个  我听到了
No, that's what he said, I heard it.
-他说你很固执  -什么鬼
- He said... pushy. - What the fuck?
当然这也很无礼
Which is also fucking rude.
他不是在特指你的逼
He doesn't mean your pussy in particular.
你们疯了对吧
You're insane, right?
-你们是不是疯了  -也许吧
- Are you fucking insane? - Probably.
那要怎么样呢
Well, what's it gonna be?
-他疯了  -操你妈  巴克斯利
- He's fucking crazy. - Fuck you, Baxley.
我感觉还好
I feel fine.
他们要射杀我
They were gonna shoot me?
为什么
Why?
也许是因为这个
Uh, maybe 'cause of this?
那我加入
Well, I guess I'm in.
离我远点
Stay the fuck away from me.
这他妈是什么
What the fuck is this?
这是什么
What is this?
-那是什么  独角兽  -独角兽
- What is that? Like a unicorn? - A unicorn.
-独角兽  -独角兽
- It's a unicorn. - A unicorn.
我做了个独角兽
I made a unicorn...
抱歉  做太烂了
I'm sorry, it's a piece of shit.
那么  我跟你们在一起有什么好处
So, what's the upside to me staying here with you guys?
也许能够活下去
Uh, maybe staying alive?
我们是士兵
We are soldiers.
我们是好人
We're the good guys, okay?
这可不一定
Well, that's debatable.
我读了你的档案  在墨西哥被害的人
I read your file. The guys in Mexico it killed?
是你的手下
They yours?
他们会需要一个替罪羊
They're gonna need a patsy for that.
看来就是我了
You're looking at him.
我猜到了
Yeah, I figured.
患有创伤后应激障碍的前任狙击手  完美
Ex-sniper with PTSD? That's actually kind of perfect.
不如你来说说
How about you telling us
你在秘密基地里做什么
what you were doing in a secret base.
周围都是一群训练有素的雇佣兵
Surrounded by trained soldiers. Mercs.
我是生物学家  他们会找我  当...
I'm a biologist, and they have me on call in case there's...
有外星接触时
contact.
我怎么跟你们说的
What did I tell you?
终结时刻  世界要终结了
End days. End days.
奈特尔斯  要是你再扯圣经的鬼话
Nettles, if you don't stop with this Bible shit,
我就把你烧死
I'm gonna set you on fire.
各位  要是我们想活下去
Guys, if we wanna keep breathing,
就得找到它
we need to find this thing.
曝光它
Expose it.
它叫掠夺者
It's called the Predator.
它狩猎人类当做娱乐
It hunts people for sport.
严格来说  它不是掠夺者  而是像...
Technically, that's not a predator. That's like...
谢谢
Thank you.
-猎人  -我说的就是这个
- It's a hunter. - I said the same thing.
像冒险家  猎人  或者说渔夫
A sportsman, or a hunter, or a fisherman.
看看你
Well, look at you...
它逃跑的时候我在场  它在找什么东西
I was there when it escaped. It's looking for something.
器械  武器
Equipment. Weapons.
我拿了它的装备
I took its gear.
什么
What?
你从它身上拿了东西
You took something from the thing?
-什么  -那样我就有证据在手了
- What? - So, I'd have evidence.
我想我知道它要去哪里了
I think I know where it's going.
什么
What?
亲爱的  你回来了
Oh, hi, honey, you're home.
-我来找一个包裹  -包裹
- I'm looking for a package. - A package?
罗利
Rory!
这里不是你的家了
Hey! This is not your house anymore!
罗利
Rory!
伙计  你在哪里
Hey, buddy. Where are ya?
他不在
He's not here.
他不在是什么意思
What do you mean, he's not here?
该死的
Oh, shit!
什么  我们买了电子游戏
What? So we ordered some video games.
不不不
No! No! No!
我寄到邮箱的目的
The whole fucking reason I sent it to a P.O. Box,
就是为了让你们远离危险
was so I didn't put you in danger.
该死的  我们必须找到他
Goddamn it, we need to find him.
等等  奎因  你吓到我了
Wait, Quinn, you're scaring me now.
我还特地说过
I specifically said
不能玩第一人称视角射击游戏  不能玩战争游戏
no first-person shooter. No combat games.
你难道就没想过他玩这种游戏
Did you ever think that maybe he plays them
是为了和他爸爸多一点联系吗
to connect with his father?
天啊  我们又开始了
Oh, my God. We're doing this again.
你能不能不要再说我...
Hey! Can you stop taking all my...
我家里的这些人是谁
Who are these people in my house?
艾米丽  疯子们  疯子们  这是艾米丽
Emily, loonies. Loonies, Emily.
晚上好
Good evening.
画上的笔触
Uh, the brushstrokes on this
非常充满活力  很棒的作品
are really dynamic. It's a wonderful piece.
好了  你得把画放下
Okay, you need to put that down.
她的右手在干什么
What exactly is she doing with her right hand?
他们是我的小队里的  都是士兵
They're my unit. They're soldiers.
海军陆战队  这是他的"小队"
Marines. There's his unit.
你好  你看起来是个很好的...
Hi. You seem like a really nice...
不  别碰我  别
Oh, no, don't touch me. No.
慢着  退后  你的小队
Hang on. Back up. Your unit?
海因斯和杜普雷怎么了
What happened to Haines and Dupree?
他们死了
They're dead.
杀了他们的那个东西正在找罗利
And the thing that killed them is out there looking for Rory.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
外面有个东西
There's something out there.
它把我的朋友们撕碎了  它是什么
It tore my friends apart. What is it?
是一个生物  不是人
Like, it's a creature. Seriously, it's not a person.
就像圣经里的
Like from the Bible.
-天启  -圣经里的
- Revelations. - From the Bible?
这是我听过最荒谬的事了
That's the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard.
是外星人
It's a space alien.
你知道乌比·戈德堡(美国黑人女演员)吗
Know who Whoopi Goldberg is?
就像是外星人版的乌比·戈德堡
It's like an alien Whoopi Goldberg.
该死的
Oh, shit!
Shit.
要地毯式搜索
I want a grid search.
分成三个队
Three teams.
-不  -不  我要跟你一起去
- No. - No, no, I'm coming with you.
不  不可以
No, nix that.
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
问题在于  我们就像是活靶子
Thing is, we're kind of moving targets.
对  以防你没注意  我们是逃犯
Yeah, in case you haven't noticed, we're fugitives.
对  再说我们要去哪里弄药和别的东西
Yeah. Plus, like where are we gonna get our meds and stuff?
我明白了  好吧  留在这儿看电视吧
I get it. Fine, stay here and watch TV.
知道吗  要是你们想四散逃跑  或是引来条子
You know what? If you try to split? Or draw the Feds?
或者你们的混蛋行为
Or if you jeopardize my son
危害到了我的儿子
by your half-assed yardbird bullshit...
我会回来  很乐意地
I will come back here, and I will happily
把你们一个个都宰了
kill every single fucking one of you.
走吧  兄弟们  我们走
Come on, brothers. Let's go.
真的吗
Seriously?
这不是我们的战斗
It's not our fight.
你丈夫是我认为的那个人吗
Is your husband the man I think he is?
你说什么
Excuse me?
请说说你丈夫是什么样的人
Tell me about your husband, please?
他是安全反狙击手
He's a security counter-sniper.
陆军游骑兵
Army Rangers.
他在五大洲
He supervised
协助指导了23次近距离精确交战
23 close precision engagements across five continents
有13次击杀记录
and he has 13 confirmed kills.
他是武装部队中仅有的同时获得过
And he is one of only 14 captains in the armed forces,
杰出服务奖章和银星奖章的
to ever receive a Distinguished Service Medal
14名上尉之一
and the Silver Star.
他也许是个差劲的丈夫
So, he might be a lousy husband,
但他是个好士兵
but he is a good soldier.
听起来他一个人能搞定
Well, sounds like he can probably take care of himself.
-没错  -天啊
- Yeah. - Jesus Christ.
我猜到了
That's what I thought.
一群怂货
Fucking pussies.
你要去哪里  奈特尔斯
Where you going, Nettles?
我不喜欢你的演说  没激励到我
I didn't like your speech. It didn't really inspire me.
但是  他叫我怂货
But... he called me a pussy
没人可以叫我怂货  所以...
and nobody calls me a pussy, so...
-滚吧  怂货  -好吧
- Fuck off, pussy. - Okay...
走吧  巴克斯  我们去找点乐子
Come on, Bax, let's go. Let's get some.
在这些陆军混蛋搞砸了一切之前
Before these army fuckers screw up the whole thing.
快  你在干什么  走啊
Come on, what are you doing? Let's move.
你也是  幸运符
You too, lucky charms.
柯伊尔  你个蠢货
Coyle, you wanker.
有机会我想
I'd like to watch TV
-和你一起看电视  -行了
- with you sometime. - Okay.
我喜欢你演说
I liked your speech.
我喜欢你家沙发
I liked the couch.
什么回事  你要干什么
Whoa, what's happening? What?
我们要去找我儿子  要干这个
Well, we're finding my son, that's what.
好了  等事情结束后...
All right, when all this is over...
用非洲食蚁兽正面上我
Fuck me in the face with an aardvark.
我只是想出名
I just want to be famous.
表面上看
Ostensibly,
如果阿甘读了盒子侧面上的字
if Forrest Gump just read the side of the box,
他肯定就能懂上面写的什么
it would tell him exactly what he would get.
"表面上看"这个词不是这么用的
You're using "Ostensibly" incorrectly.
这是给我的吗
Is this for me?
这简直和小丑车大相庭径
This is like the reverse of a clown car.
好了  内布拉斯加
All right, Nebraska,
我们去找点车  别搞太炫酷
let's find some wheels, nothing flashy.
收到
Copy.
好了  找到我的儿子
All right. Find my son.
凯西  你跟我来
Casey, you're with me.
我们走
Let's go.
屁股蛋儿
Hey, ass-burger.
你要打扮成谁呢
What are you supposed to be?
别来烦我
Leave me alone.
不然呢  你就要洗五百次手吗
Or what? You'll wash our hands five hundred times?
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick or treat?
怎么了  哥们儿
What's the matter, dude?
让你捣蛋  小混蛋
Here's a treat, you little shit.
我发现一名少年
I got a male juvenile.
十到十二岁
10 to 12 years old.
胳膊上戴着那装备
Metal cast on his arm.
麦肯纳  你听到了吗
Yo, McKenna, do you hear that?
从我车前跑过
Ran right in front of my car.
往东走到伍德拉夫路上了
Moving east on Woodruff.
重复  往东走到伍德拉夫路上了
Repeat, moving east on Woodruff.
内布拉斯加  你搞到车了吗
Nebraska, you got wheels?
我搞到车了  很炫酷的车
Yeah, I got wheels. Something flashy.
听着  那孩子受惊逃跑了
Listen, the kid's spooked, he's rabbiting.
他往那边走了  附近有没有他熟悉的地方
Where's he headed? Where's some place he knows?
他在那里
There he is.
爸爸
Dad!
你好吗  伙计
How you doing, buddy, huh?
我很好
I'm good.
上  上
Move! Move!
博士  照顾好我的孩子
Hey, Doc, come get my kid.
我们走  我们走  我们走
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
该死
Oh, shit!
麦肯纳
McKenna!
快躲  快躲
Take cover! Take cover!
威廉姆斯  离开那里
Williams! Get the fuck out of there!
你在干什么  离开那里
What are you doing? Get out of there!
该死
Oh, shit!
好吧
Oh. Okay.
博士  那些可怕的东西是什么
Doc, the dreads. What's that all about?
我不知道  可能是某种感应接收器
I don't know. Maybe, like, sensor receptors.
就像触须一样
Kind of like cat whiskers.
搞什么...我在取样本呢
Whoa! What the-- I'm getting a sample.
这是一只外星狗
It's a fucking space dog.
你没事吧
You okay? Huh?
怎么  你妈妈现在还给你剪头发吗
What, is your mom cutting your hair now?
你在开玩笑吗  这是
You kidding me? This is
-千载难逢的机会  -闭嘴  请闭嘴
- a once-in-a-lifetime moment. - Shut up. Please shut up.
我只想要一个小小的样本
All I wanted was a little sample.
请闭嘴
Please shut up.
我只想要一份该死的样本
All I wanted was a goddamn fucking sample.
过来
Come here.
样本
Sample.
-给  -谢谢
- There you go. - Thank you.
-不客气  -该死的外星狗  伙计
- You're welcome. - Fucking space dog, man.
-伙计  你得...  -这真是
- My man, you need to-- - It's a fucking--
我不行  我不行
I can't. I can't.
-冷静点  -我做不到
- Get it together. - I can't do this.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
Fucking hell!
操
Fuck!
快上
Go now! Please!
罗利
Rory!
朝他开枪  朝他开枪
Shoot him! Shoot him!
不不不
Hey! No! No! No!
No! No! No!
操  不不不
Oh, fuck, fuck. No, no, no!
屌  屌  操  屌
Cock! Cock! Fuck! Dick!
吃我屌  操  该死
Suck! Suck my cock! Fuck! Goddamn it!
快跑  快跑
Go! Go! Go!
我拉他  我拉他
I got him! I got him!
快走  快走  跟着威廉姆斯  跟着威廉姆斯
Go, go, go! On Williams! On Williams!
罗利
Rory!
-快躲  -快走
- Take cover! - Move!
快走
Go! Go!
快
Come on!
顺便  占星师发现我时
FYI, back at Stargazer,
我手无寸铁没有防护  它就从我身边走过去了
I was naked and unarmed, it walked right past me.
你能让你的孩子控制一下那个疯狂的东西吗
Can you tell your kid to tone down the psychosis, please?
好吧  来吧  来吧
All right, let's do this. Let's do this.
等等  做什么
Wait, and do what?
我们可以
You know, we could keep running,
或者我们可以把他想要的东西给他
or we give him back what he wants.
什么  就是这个吗
What, this is it?
天啊  该死
Oh, my God. Shit.
该死
Shit.
不不不  快走  快走
No, no, no! Move! Move! Move!
快来
Hey, come on.
你没事吧
You good?
不行了
Fucked!
我们赶紧离开这里
Let's get the fuck out of here.
奈迪  去开车
Netty, get the vehicle.
-其他人跟我来  -收到
- The rest of you on me. - Copy.
后退
Move back.
不不不
No! No! No!
不
No!
小心
Incoming!
搞什么
What the fuck?
过来  快来  快来  我们走
Come here! Roll out! Roll out, let's go!
我们走  我们走  我们走
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
-走  -快走  快走
- Move! - Move out, move out!
快  快走
Move! Move out!
-快走  -快走
- Let's go! - Let's move!
走  快走
Go, go, go! Let's go!
快走
Let's go!
走
Move!
快点
Come on!
快点  上车  走
Move! Come on, get in! Come on!
坐下
Sit down!
好了  好了  好了
Good! Good! Good!
走  全上了
Go! Last man!
走  走  走
Go! Go! Go!
那个大家伙是什么
What's the big one?
那大家伙是什么  博士  那是雄性吗
What's the big one, Doc? Is that like the male?
他一点都不在乎我们
He didn't even give a shit about us.
只想杀戮
Just wanted to kill that thing.
你看到了  对吗
You saw that, right?
伙计们  你们看到了吗  他
Guys! Did you see that? He--
他从皮下伸出了外骨
He grew an exoskeleton under his fucking skin.
他们现在是在相互追杀吗
What, are they hunting each other now?
我们还在进行调查
We're still sorting through it right now.
-是我  -告诉我他没事
- Hey, it's me. -Tell me he's okay.
他没事  我准备把他送回家了
He's fine. I'm going to bring him back.
没事  什么都别说  保重
It's okay, don't say anything, just be safe.
不  住手
Hey, no! Don't do that!
什么  喂
What? Hello?
该死
Damn it.
我们家可不是好惹的
You guys fucked with the wrong family.
-多高  -目击证人说大概十一英尺
- How tall? - Witnesses say 11 feet.
那真是太高了
That's pretty fucking tall.
好吧
Okay.
-我真是操了  -长官
- Fucked that nigga up. - Sir?
没什么
Nothing.
小心点  长官
I'd be careful with that, sir.
你知道我是怎么想的吗
You know what I think?
我觉得这是一只失控的逃亡者
I think this one went rogue. A runner.
那个大块头呢
Hmm. And the big one?
他是一名追踪者
He's a tracker.
被派来干掉他的
Sent to take that one out.
应该算是星际警察追捕犯人
Some kind of interstellar cops and robbers.
现在他要去找那艘失踪的飞船
Now he's going after that missing ship.
以及船上的东西
And whatever's on board.
我要那艘该死的船
I want that fucking ship.
我们在棒球场
We're in the ballpark.
麦肯纳上尉的儿子
Captain McKenna's son?
经他母亲确认
Mother confirms.
操作系统在他手上
He has the operating system.
-不是吧  -他以为那是个电子游戏
- Get the fuck out of here. - Thought it was a video game.
我们找到那孩子就能找到飞船
So, we find the kid, we find the ship.
那我们为什么还傻站在这里
What the fuck we still standing here for?
你不想知道那是什么东西吗
You don't want to know what that one is?
我知道那是什么  这大块头是捕猎者
I know what it is. Our big boy's a hunter.
他还带来了自己的猎犬
He brought his dogs with him.
不  应该是
No, it had to be like
什么政府实验之类的
a government experiment or some shit.
什么机器人之类的
Like a robot, or whatever.
奈特尔斯  你他妈是白痴吗
Nettles, are you fucking retarded, man?
你能不能别用这个词
Use another word, would ya?
对啊  能不能考虑一下别人
Yeah, man. Show a little sensitivity.
他儿子是个白痴
His son's retarded.
来
Here you go.
他偶尔是会变成这样
He does this from time to time.
给他一点时间
Just give him a minute.
林奇
Hey, Lynch.
这两个家伙是怎么回事
What's the deal with these two?
柯伊尔烧毁了一辆他自己的车吗
Coyle lit up one of his own vehicles?
2009年的事了  出了问题  死了六个
Back in '09, yeah. It was bad business. Six dead.
没有幸存者吗
What, no survivors?
只有一个
Yeah, there was one.
真他妈浪漫
It's fucking romantic.
你在开玩笑吗  他们是朋友吗
Are you kidding me, they're friends?
想象一下
Picture it.
军事审判  坐在法庭外
Military inquiries, sitting outside courtroom,
等着进去  坐在一起
waiting to go in, side by side,
-一天天的  -一天天的
- day after fucking day. - After fucking day.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
就是疯子
It's the loonies.
好了  孩子
All right, kid.
我和你妈妈通过话了
I've talked to your mother.
她很好
She's doing fine.
妈妈说你是一名杀人犯
Mom says you're a killer.
我是一名士兵
Well, I'm a soldier.
有什么区别
What's the difference?
当你喜欢做士兵时
Well, when you like it,
才能算得上是一名杀人犯
that's when you're a killer.
你没事吧
Are you good?
抱歉  我没有成长
Sorry I never grew up.
就是没变成你想要的那样
You know... the way you wanted.
告诉你一个秘密
Tell you a secret.
事实上  孩子
Truth is, kid,
我从来没有成长成我想要的样子
I never grew up the way I wanted.
我们会被杀吗
Are we gonna get killed?
不
Nope.
来  起来
Come on. Get up.
我单身  不知道你知不知道
I'm single. I don't know if you knew that.
嗯  我看得出来你单身
No, I could tell that you're single.
我们有很多共同点
We got so much stuff in common, you know...
你喜欢音乐  我也喜欢音乐  你喜欢音乐的吧
You like music, I like music. You like music, right?
-该死  -怎么了
- Shit. - What?
这不仅仅是脊髓液
This is more than spinal fluid.
什么意思
What does that mean?
如果我想得没错
If I'm right,
他们正在自我升级
they're trying to upgrade themselves.
麦肯纳  我有发现
McKenna, I got something.
我觉得掠夺者一族
I think I know what they're up to
到底想要干什么了
on Predator World these days.
看  这是在掠夺者的神经丛里找到的
You see this? They found this in the Predator's plexus.
你记不记得我告诉过你
So, remember how I told you
他们会取走人们的脊椎
how they take people's spines, right?
是的  当做战利品
Yeah, for trophies.
没错  取走他们去过的每个星球上
Yes! Yes! From the strongest, smartest,
最强壮  最聪明者的脊椎
most dangerous species on every planet they visit.
采集高级物种的
Collecting survival traits
生存性状
from the most high-end specimens.
我觉得他们想要进行杂交
I think they're attempting hybridization.
你在说什么胡话
You're just pulling this out of your ass.
你没看到那个新的掠夺者吗
Did you not see the new Predator?
他进化了
It's evolving.
或者被升级了
Or being upgraded.
那小子
That little boy
鼓捣明白了外星技术
managed to figure out alien technology.
很多专家认为
You know, a lot of experts say that
自闭症可能并不是一种疾病
being on the spectrum isn't really a disorder.
其实是进入了进化链上的下个阶段
It's actually the next step in the evolutionary chain.
喂  搞什么
Hey, yo! What the fuck?
放开我
Get the fuck away from me!
凯西
Yo! Casey!
凯西  进来
Casey, get inside.
凯西
Casey!
冷静点  冷静点
Hey, hey, hey! Calm down! Calm down! Calm down!
凯西  听着
Casey! Look.
我觉得这玩意一直在跟着我们
I think this thing's been following us, all right?
让开  奈迪
Move, Netty!
-外星狗  -让开  奈迪
- Space dog! - Move, Netty!
操
Fuck that.
想都别想
Hey! You had your fucking chance.
我只是想说  这小家伙能怎么样呢
Look, I'm just saying, what the fuck is it gonna do?
也许我们能利用它之类的
You know, maybe we can use it, or something?
我们怎么办  我们拿它怎么办
Okay, what are we doing? What are we doing with it?
我们要研究它  我们要这么做
We're gonna study it. That's what we're gonna do with it.
有什么好研究的  只知道威廉姆斯
What's to learn? Except Williams sucks
连它的脑袋都打不中
at shooting shit in the head.
威廉姆斯  你让它变成痴呆了
Williams, you lobotomized him.
好吧  新规矩  谁都不准朝我的狗开枪
Okay, new rule. No one shoots my fucking dog.
好了  正式不行了
There it is. It's official.
你说得对  我们可以利用它
You were right, we can use this.
该死
Shit.
奈迪  那是什么
Netty, what is that?
所有人做好准备
Everybody, tighten up.
-小家伙  过来  -那是一架EC130
- Little man, come here. - That's an EC-130.
不是平民
That's not civilian.
我孩子在这里  别想在这里交火
You are not starting a firefight with my kid here.
进来
There you go.
你想帮忙的话就去搞架飞机和弹药
Do you wanna help? Go get a helicopter and some pyro.
好吧  交给我吧
All right! On me!
快走
Now go!
-凯西  我马上回来  -不  你不会的
- Casey! I'll be right back! - No, you won't.
等等  看到了吗
Hold on. Hey. See this?
来  过来  过来
Come on. Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
去捡
Fetch!
在哪里
Where is it?
什么在哪里
Where's what?
那装置
The device.
就在这里
It goes, right in here.
第一位掠夺者  一号
Okay, so, the first Predator, Thing One.
他为什么要来到地球
Why'd he come here? To Earth?
你所谓的一号
The "Thing One", as you called him,
是乘坐一艘被侵占的飞船来的
arrived in a hijacked spacecraft.
我们觉得那艘飞船上有东西
We think there's something on it.
他不希望落入敌手的东西
Something he didn't want his enemies to have.
等等  他的敌人
Wait, enemies?
其他掠夺者  就像那个大块头
Other Predators. Like that big one.
他带来了什么  给人类的礼物吗
So, he brought some what? Gift for the human race?
我能帮你找到  我们可以分析...
I'll help you find it. We can analyze it...
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
他们为什么会来这里
Why are they here?
你还记得几年前女主人面包破产时
You remember a few years back when Hostess went bust?
出现的糕点大抢购吧
There was a run on Twinkies?
沿岸进行抢购
Snapped up from coast-to-coast.
趁店还开着
Get 'em while they still last.
记得吗
Remember?
气温变化会让这个星球过多久后变得无法居住
How long before climate change renders this planet unlivable?
两代
Two generations?
还是一代
One?
所以他们来得更频繁了
That's why their visits are increasing?
他们想趁我们灭绝前
They're trying to snap up
带走我们最好的基因
all of our best DNA before we're gone.
与他们自己结合  然后鸠占鹊巢
Adapt themselves with it and then move in.
我们算是濒危物种了  他们很清楚
We're an endangered species, and they know it.
温室环境最适合他们
They thrive in a hothouse environment.
也许他们想要住到我们这
Maybe they want to move into ours.
那个死去的掠夺者
And that dead Predator
给我们带来了阻止他们的办法
was bringing us a way to stop them.
你当初在信里就隐瞒了这个东西
You've hidden this thing before in the mail.
这次在哪里呢
So, where is it this time?
你妈屁眼里
Your mother's ass.
等等  我不小心说出口了吗
Wait, did I say that out loud?
不不不  你不能看这个
Hey! Hey! Hey! No, no, no. That is not for you.
这是我儿子的
That is my son's,
你看就是侵犯了他的个人隐私
and you are violating his privacy reading that.
你们俩得赶紧离开这里
You both need to leave right now.
女士  我不想把你铐起来
Ma'am, I don't wanna restrain you.
真的吗  那你不如来试试
Really? Well, why don't you try?
(罗利  麦肯纳)
你还没有找到飞船吗
You haven't found the spacecraft?
我们为什么要破解入口码
Why are we trying to crack the entry code?
因为等我们找到后  要是我们能
Because when we do find it, wouldn't it be great
进到这该死的东西里  是不是很棒
if we could get into the fucking thing?
那是什么
What's that?
一张地图
A map.
通往哪里的地图
A map to what?
让我们知道这地方是什么
...give us a clue of where this place is,
也许我们能想办法进去
maybe we can try to get into it.
但如果你什么都不告诉我们  我们就进不去
But if you don't give us anything, we can't get in!
罗利  我叫威尔
Hey, Rory, I'm Will.
你好吗
How you doing?
我知道你知道飞船在哪里
I understand you know where the spaceship is.
明天去打高尔夫吗
Golf tomorrow?
可以啊
Why not?
你们俩没看过我的档案  对吗
You two never read my file, did ya?
你为什么这么说
What makes you say that?
因为你们在计划明天的安排了
'Cause you two morons are making plans for tomorrow.
最糟的是
The worst part is,
你们让我骗了我儿子
you're making me lie to my son.
你骗了他什么
What lie did you tell him, hmm?
说我不会喜欢这样
That I won't enjoy this.
拜托  不要
Hey, please, don't.
听着  我不知道他们和你说了什么
Look, I don't know what they told you...
我们能不能等一下  等等
Can you just wait for a second? Just wait!
不不不
No, no, no!
不
No.
上帝啊
Jeez!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
内布拉斯加
Nebraska!
-什么事  -你刚杀人了吗
- Yeah? - You just kill somebody?
他可不怎么样
Well, he ain't well.
放开我朋友
Untie my friend.
他们抓走了罗利  我们得赶紧走
They got Rory. We gotta move.
该死  他们揍了你吗
Shit, they rough you up?
我经历过更猛烈的毒打
Did worse on myself, back in the day.
你打算怎么处置这家伙
What do you want to do with this guy?
抱歉  伙计  这问题真蠢
Sorry, buddy, that was a dumb question.
没错  这问题真蠢
Yeah, that was a dumb question.
凯西
Casey!
你有兴趣离开这里吗
Can I interest you in getting the fuck out of here?
我的中间名就是"离开这里"
"Getting the fuck out of here" Is my middle name.
我以为盖洛德(基王)这个名字已经够烂了
And I thought Gaylord was bad.
怎么了
What? What's wrong?
好了
Whew! All right.
让我先把这些包里的东西拿出来
Hey! Just let me unpack this.
你说我儿子被带到一艘飞船上去了
You're saying my son's headed towards a spaceship
还有一个十英尺高的外星人也是
and so is a 10-foot alien.
其实是十一英尺
Uh, 11, actually.
我以前是个承包商
Used to be a contractor.
那玩意是个混种的  那是什么意思
This thing is a hybrid? What does that mean?
说明它的基因简单明了
Meaning it's the Chinese menu of DNA.
整合了最致命的基因  来自全...
Comprised of the deadliest species in the entire...
全宇宙  对吗
In the entire universe, yeah?
-全银河系  -什么
- Galaxy. - What?
银河系就有2500亿颗行星
Galaxy. 250 billion stars.
何必要去整个宇宙  就是这么随便一说
Why go universe? Just saying.
我的老天爷啊
Jesus Tap-Dancing Christ!
这是你搞的飞机吗
That's what you asked for?
那也行吧
Yeah, that'll do.
快上来
Saddle up!
只能搞到这样的了
It's the best we could do, man.
上来  上
Go ahead. Go!
就这些了吗  还有
That's it? Another one.
还有
The other one!
走吧  去救我的孩子
Come on. Let's go get my kid.
我想了想  觉得我们可能会死
Figured something out. I think we're gonna die.
我们要去追杀什么  和军队战斗吗
We're gonna go hunt and fight the what, the army?
我们不要和军队战斗
We're not gonna fight the army...
还有外太空来的什么家伙
And some fucking people from space!
你想跟我说活命
You wanna talk survival, huh?
好吧
Fine!
你昨天还在一辆囚车上
You, yesterday, you were on a prison bus
苦苦哀求
barking to yourself,
现在你手上拿着一把枪
now you got a gun in your hand.
看看是谁活了下来
Who's a survivor now?
我们就算脑袋中弹
We put bullets in our head
也要走到医院
and walk to the fucking hospital.
我们是士兵
We're soldiers!
奈特尔斯  我们在哪里
Nettles, what's our 20?
我能追踪到你儿子所在的直升机
I can follow your boy's chopper.
我锁定了它的频率
I locked into its frequency.
围栏通电
Fence is hot!
怎么样  伙计
What do you say, buddy?
你觉得你能带我们进去吗
You think you can get us in there?
因为我可不敢确定
Because I'm not sure that you can.
激将法用得不错
Nice reverse psychology.
我也会
I can do that, too.
别干你自己
Don't go fuck yourself.
真棒  来吧
That's good. Come on.
很好  快准备好了  五分钟
Good. Almost up and running. Five minutes.
马上来
Right on.
这是一个破译部门  罗利
It's a translator unit, Rory.
自从1987年七
Been trying to figure out
我们就一直想弄清楚
what these bird-chirping motherfuckers
这些鸟叫到底什么意思
been saying since '87.
给哈佛语言学学院
Gave the Harvard School of Linguistics
拨了十亿
a billion-dollar grant.
看  小心点  来
Voila. Watch your step, come on.
该死  孩子  真不知道你哪来的本事
Goddamn, kid, I don't know where you get it from.
将破译器安在主机上
Put the translator into the mainframe.
全部下载
Download everything.
那里面有什么
What the hell's inside there?
这是占星师项目的所有物
It's property of Project Stargazer.
就是这么简单
That's what the fuck it is.
三号警报  三号警报
Code three. Code three.
南边围栏有动静
We have motion at the south fence line.
派一支武装小队过去查看
Send a fireteam to check it out.
是我爸爸  他要来救我了
That's my dad. He's gonna come save me now.
是吗
Oh, is he?
他是这个打算吗
Is that what he's gonna do?
我告诉你  伙计
I'll tell you what, buddy...
如果真的是你爸爸
if it is your daddy,
我希望真的就是他
and I truly hope that it is...
那他肯定就是
he's gotta be just about
我见过最愚蠢的笨蛋
the dumbest motherfucker I've ever met.
一名突击狙击手居然能触发报警器
I mean, a Ranger sniper tripping wire sensors?
他肯定是在...
He's gotta be...
声东击西
creating a diversion.
字幕
It's a fucking diversion.
该死
Oh, shit!
你好
Wow. Howdy.
怎么  你要用麻醉枪杀了我们吗
What, are you gonna kill us with a fucking tranq gun?
你们抓走了我的儿子  没错
You took my boy, so yeah.
早跟你说了
Told you.
拿着  儿子
Take this, son.
你疯了吗  我们的人把你包围了
You outta your mind? We literally have you surrounded.
所以你要跟我来
That's why you're coming with me.
我只要带我儿子走  没人会死
I just want the boy. Nobody's got to die.
爸爸
Dad?
从现在开始
From here forward.
不要看死人
Don't look at the dead guy.
感觉真棒
That was pretty good.
你没事吧  吓到你了吗
You all right? Did I get you?
不  我没事
No, I'm good.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
去你妈的  我从来没离开过
Fuck you. I never left.
你敢说话
You open your mouth,
我就把你的脑子轰飞
I'm gonna blow your brains right through it.
来  躲到我后面
Come on, just get behind me.
所有单位注意  他们挟持了特雷格
All units. They got Traeger.
他们挟持了特雷格
They got Traeger.
我们走  我们走
Let's go. Let's go.
要他们把枪放下
Just tell them to put the guns down.
跟他们说
Tell them!
如果麦肯纳上尉在十秒内
If Captain McKenna doesn't lower his weapon
不放下武器
in the next 10 seconds...
就打这孩子的膝盖  你觉得可以吗
shoot the kid's knees out. That work for you?
这真是个糟糕的主意
Oh, that's a really bad idea.
我的人已经安插到每个角落
My guys got this place covered on every angle.
真好笑  然而我并不在乎
That's a funny story. See, I don't give a shit.
十
10.
九
Nine.
八
Eight.
七
Seven.
拜托  赶紧下命令啊  伙计
Come on, you just give the fucking word, man.
六  五
Six. Five.
该死
Oh, shit!
过来  儿子
Come on, son!
干掉他们
Take them down!
蹲下  长官
Get down, sir.
走  儿子  走
Let's go, son. Go!
快点  快点
Come on. Come on.
拿着这个
Okay, take this.
你想消失
You wanna vanish,
就会真的消失  儿子  明白吗
you really vanish, son, you understand?
好了  我们要回家了  我保证
All right, we're going home. I promise you.
它来了
It's here.
不  不  不
No! No! No!
快点  从那边过去
Come on, go around the end there!
瞄准他  瞄准他
Stay on him! Stay on him!
快快快
Move, move, move!
-打中他了吗  -打中了
- You got him? - Yeah!
后退
Stay back.
趴下  趴下
Get down! Get down!
停火  停火  停火
Cease fire! Cease fire! Cease fire!
好吧
All right.
麦肯纳
Hey, McKenna.
讲点道理  你们有六个人  我们有七个
Be reasonable. There's six of you, seven of us.
该死
Fuck!
你数学是谁教的
Who taught you math?
你可不是唯一的狙击手  小白脸
You ain't the only fucking sniper, white boy.
你可以离开  上尉
You can walk away from this, Captain.
我只想要这艘飞船
I just want the ship.
-爸爸  他撒谎  -对
- Dad, he's lying. - Yeah.
麦肯纳  我不喜欢这样
McKenna! I don't like this.
他在里面干什么
What's he doing in there?
他在使用破译机
It's using the translator.
你们好  我很喜欢
Hello. I have enjoyed
看你们自相残杀
watching you kill each other.
我是来破坏这个舱体的
I came here to destroy this vessel.
不能落入你们手中
You cannot have it.
你们只能逃走
What you can do is run.
我检测到你们中有一人是真正的战士
I detect one among you who is a true warrior.
叫麦肯纳的那位
The one called McKenna.
他会是你们的首领
He will be your leader.
我想要得到他
He will be my prize.
我会给你们时间优势
I offer time advantage.
走
Go.
时间优势是什么东西
What the fuck is time advantage?
先跑一步吗
Like a head start?
我会在车上醒过来
I'm gonna wake up on a bus.
我出来了
I'm coming out!
我们上
We're in.
-巴克斯利  -该死
- Baxley! - Shit!
看好了再扔  混蛋
Watch where the fuck you're throwing, dickhead.
好的
Will do.
我们分头行动  往12个不同的方向跑
Okay, so we split up. 12 different directions.
-他想要的事麦肯纳  -不不不
- McKenna's the one he wants. - No, no, no!
我们一起行动  不然他会一个个干掉我们
We stay together, or it'll take us one by one.
他说得对  这是他们的惯用手法
He's right. It's their MO.
-能不能男人点  -什么都发动不起来
- Grow a dick, will you? - Nothing's starting!
混蛋  他肯定黑入了这些车辆
Son of a bitch. He must have hacked the vehicles.
如果你们能去直升机那里  往南开两英里
If we can get to the helicopter, go two klicks north.
好的
Got you.
等着一切结束了  我们俩得好好解决一下
When this is over, you and me, we're gonna dance.
随时奉陪
I got my shoes all picked out.
好
All right.
-操  -不不不  不要
- Fuck. - No, no, no! Don't.
小家伙  去捡
Here, boy. Fetch.
去吧  小家伙
Here, boy.
来
Here you go.
那可是非常珍贵的武器
That was a valuable weapon.
我们走  他回来追我们的
Let's go. He'll be coming for us.
把工具包给我
Give me the goody bag.
万圣节夜  这个炸掉了一幢房子
Hey. On Halloween, this blew up a whole house.
-你怎么发射的  -不用发射
- How do you shoot it? - You don't.
遭到袭击后它会自动开火
It just fires by itself when it's being attacked.
真的吗  该死
Seriously? Oh, shit.
我听到一些动静
I heard something.
伙计  那是掠夺者的科技
Hey, man. That's Predator technology.
该死
Fuck.
那...那会回来的
That-- It's gonna come back.
你的手腕上有捕捉器
You got, uh, a catcher on the wrist.
会回来的
That's gonna come back.
不
No!
安静  安静
Quiet. Quiet.
-让我看看  让我看看  -我的手
- Let me see. Let me see. - My fucking hand.
-该死  -我的手
- Shit. - My fucking hand.
必须要安静
Gotta be quiet.
快走
Moving!
不不不  这边  这边
No, no, no! This way. This way. This way.
这边有路
There's a clearing up ahead.
林奇伪造了一些痕迹  掩盖我们的行踪
Lynch left some pyro up there. To cover our retreat.
我们去找到那混蛋
Let's find it and trap the motherfucker.
你们去设好陷阱  我们把他引过来
You guys go set it up. We'll lure him in.
-谁  -你和我
- Who? - You and me.
-行吧  -好
- Yeah? - All right.
-好吧  -我们走
- Yeah. - Let's go.
走吧
Come on.
我能和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
什么叫我们
What's this "We" Shit?
难道你要记一辈子吗  柯伊尔
What, are you gonna live forever, Coyle?
-冷静点  -冷静点
- Just calm down. - Calm down?
你要我冷静点  行啊  谢了  抽脸怪
Me, calm down? Yeah, okay, thanks, twitchy.
快  这边  快快快
Move, move, move! Up here. Up, up, up.
该死
Shit!
去他妈的
Okay, fuck this.
混蛋
Hey! Asshole!
你在搞什么
What the fuck was that?
给你活下来的机会
It's a chance for you to survive.
去吧  交给我吧
Go! I got this.
这简直是我听过最蠢的话
That's the stupidest fucking thing I've ever heard.
来抓我们啊  混蛋
Come and get us, asshole!
遇敌
Contact!
-外星人  -遇敌
- Alien! - Contact!
-遇敌  -外星人
- Contact! - Alien!
-遇敌  -他来了
- Contact! - He's coming!
来啊  来啊  来啊
Come on. Come on. Come on.
烧他
Light him up!
柯伊尔
Coyle!
巴克斯  不
Bax, no!
特雷格
Traeger!
巴克斯利
Baxley!
死吧
Die!
该死
Oh, shit.
操
Fuck.
上  上
Move, move!
-奈特尔斯  -上
- Nettles! - Let's go!
麦肯纳
McKenna.
罗利
Rory.
我爱你
I love you.
你要找的人是我
Hey! I'm the one you want.
这边  过来  你...
Right here! Come on! You--
爸爸
Dad!
不
No!
爸爸
Dad!
-不  不  不  -麦肯纳
- No! No! No! - McKenna
不  不
No! No!
我恨你  你这个愚蠢的...
I hate you, you stupid fucking...
不  不
No! No!
他说他想要我
He said he wanted me.
他说他想要的是我
He said he wanted me!
不  他说他想要的是麦肯纳
No. He said he wanted McKenna.
进入了进化链上的下个阶段
The next step in the evolutionary chain.
不是你的  是你儿子
Not you. Your son.
他要飞走了
Yo, he's taking off.
不
No!
来吧  伙计  来吧
Come on, man. Come on.
来吧
Come on.
干掉他
Let's take it down!
来吧
Come on!
站稳了
Hang on!
操  内布拉斯加
Fuck! Nebraska!
我抓到你了
I got you!
爸爸  他要启动防御力场了  小心
Dad, there's a force field coming online. Look out!
伙计们  有东西来了
Guys! Something's coming!
快躲开
Go!
奈迪
Netty!
操
Fuck!
奈迪
Netty!
不  兄弟
No, no, no! Bro!
兄弟
Bro.
不
No.
操
Fuck!
该死
Shit!
罗利
Rory!
扔过来
Toss it!
你到底是什么
What are you?
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
我的小队
My unit.
奈特尔斯
Nettles.
柯伊尔
Coyle.
你也看到林奇的牌了
I see you saw Lynch's card.
巴克斯利一直带着这个
Baxley had this the whole time.
内布拉斯加的坏习惯
Nebraska's bad habit.
儿子
Son...
这是一群不会被任何人知晓的人
these are the ones that no one's gonna remember.
除了我们
Just us.
我们让他们安息吧
What do you say we put them to rest?
麦肯纳上尉
Captain McKenna.
我是山田由弘
Hiroshi Yamada.
-先生  -首先
- Sir. - First things first.
我想谢谢你栽培出这么优秀的孩子
I want to say thank you for having such a great kid.
他很喜欢这里
He loves it here.
他很特别  怎么样了  医生
Yeah, he's something else. What do we got, Doctor?
我想你现在应该知道了
Well, I assume that you know by now,
第一位掠夺者不是来这里猎杀我们的
but the first Predator, it didn't come here to hunt us.
-他带来了一些东西  -没错
- He brought something. - Exactly.
想听好消息吗
Now, you want to hear the good news?
送来的东西完好无损
The cargo survived.
某种自动防故障装置
With some sort of fail-safe.
在强化版铁血战至炸掉飞船之前
Before the upgrade Predator blew up the ship,
一架救生舱脱离了
a pod escaped.
弹射出去  保住了那东西
Jettisoned. Saved itself.
看来他不想冒任何风险
It seems that our boy wasn't taking any chances.
他就想把这个交到我们手上
He wanted us to have this.
你到底在这里干什么的来着
What is it again you do here, exactly?
他是全世界头号神经机械学权威
He's the world's number one authority on cybernetics.
孩子
Hey, kiddo.
很棒吧
Pretty cool, huh?
很棒  你都有自己的办公桌了
Pretty cool. You got your own desk.
我一定会告诉妈妈的
I'll make sure to tell Mom.
这就是他送给人类的礼物吗
So, this is his gift to humankind?
-后退  -小心
- Get back! - Look out!
所有人  后退
Everyone, stand back!
后退  赶紧疏散
Stand back! Clear the area!
爸爸  舱体给我发了一则信息
Dad, the pod sent me a message.
-罗利  舱体里有什么  -不知道
- Rory, what's in that pod? - Don't know!
该死
Oh, wow... Oh, shit!
-它有名字  -名字  什么名字
- It's got a name! - Name? What name?
我觉得应该要叫做
I guess you'd call it,
掠夺者杀手
the Predator Killer.
-带他离开这里  -跟着我  快走
- Get him out of here! - Come with me. Let's go.
后退  疏散区域
Get back. Clear the area.
全体注意
Eyes on it.
不管这是什么  好像处于休眠期
Whatever it is, it appears to be dormant.
我想这应该需要...
I assume it needs to be...
注意  瞄准
Eyes on. Keep your weapons trained.
放开我  拿下来
Get it off! Get it off me!
那是什么
What the hell is that?
那是我的新战服  宝贝
That's my new suit, bubba.
希望能伸展到42码
I hope they got it in a 42 long.